Contact

suzana_asani@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ suzanaquickrn (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care

Patient Safety

Accreditation

Certifications

Studor Training

CPHQ (Certified Professional Healthcare Quality)- NAHQ

CPPS (Certified Professional Patient Safety)

LEAN SIx Sigma Green Belt Certified (ASQ)

Publications

Cardiac care: Managing postoperative bleeding

Suzana (Suzy) Quick

Suzy Quick, RN, BSN, MSN, CPHQ, CPPS, CLSSGB, past CCRN Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Summary

Seasoned critical care RN with a passion for patient safety, healthcare quality and performance improvement. Many years of supporting large scale national federal contracts related to acute care patient safety/quality and health equity/reducing health disparities.

- Mastered (MSN) Prepared Seasoned Critical Care Heart/Lung Transplant Registered Nurse (RN)
- Certified Professional in Healthcare Quality (CPHQ)
- Certified Professional in Patient Safety (CPPS)
- Certified Lean Six Sigma Green Belt (CLSSGB)

Experience

Qlarant

Health Systems Improvement Advisor December 2013 - Present (6 years 7 months)

Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Adventist HealthCare
RN Quality and Safety
September 2011 - December 2013 (2 years 4 months)
Rockville MD

Tampa General Hospital
Critical Care Registered Nurse
September 2000 - May 2010 (9 years 9 months)
Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

(1000 Bed Level I Trauma Center Teaching Hospital University of South Florida)

Heart/Lung Transplant Center US/Beacon Award Winning Unit/Magnet Hospital

Cardio/Thoracic Surgery Heart and Lung Transplant, ECMO, VAD, ICU Critical Care Recovery

Charge Nurse/Lead Preceptor

Adventist LaGrange Memorial Hospital, Inc. Registered Nurse Pediatrics/Adult Med-Surg July 1997 - June 1999 (2 years)

Largrange IL

Education

Chamberlain College of Nursing
MSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011)

Morton College

ADN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1998)